{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_9_R2QZDU",
                "player_12_R2QZDU",
                "player_5_R2QZDU",
                "player_6_R2QZDU",
                "player_11_R2QZDU",
                "player_7_R2QZDU"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                9,
                12,
                5,
                6,
                11,
                7
            ],
            "animation": [
                "stand",
                "crouch",
                "stand",
                "crouch",
                "stand",
                "liedown"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair.",
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair.",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories.",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A man with short black hair, wearing a white button-up shirt, dark pants, and black shoes. Light skin tone.",
                "A bald man with glasses, dark complexion, wearing a black turtleneck, suit, and shoes"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -47368.16,
                    16339.902,
                    -22529.0,
                    0,
                    -140.35259777621815,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -47484.018,
                    16425.874,
                    -22529.458,
                    0,
                    -176.3174527801598,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -47569.126,
                    16294.553,
                    -22526.699,
                    0,
                    -171.7838999162221,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -47817.717,
                    16488.183,
                    -22529.317,
                    0,
                    -77.17389755368299,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -47103.315,
                    16229.582,
                    -22526.813,
                    0,
                    -13.76069615331781,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -47683.24,
                    15873.79,
                    -22526.008,
                    0,
                    -176.7906027751099,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -47878.257,
            15883.555,
            -23023.943
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1063.6134580893195
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -47988.854,
            16048.379,
            -22522.576,
            0,
            25.093778001174623,
            0
        ],
        [
            -46751.942,
            16353.015,
            -23256.47,
            0,
            -174.1032988756655,
            0
        ],
        [
            -47938.691,
            16489.915,
            -22529.287,
            0,
            -26.28867257087752,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many humans are currently standing in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals are in a crouch position among the group?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many women are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Among all the men in the scene, how many are not bald?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many individuals in the scene possess a medium skin color?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Excluding the person who is bald, how many people are in the scene?",
                "answer": "five"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene have a light skin color?",
                "answer": "two"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. sit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. walk"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. stand",
                    "C. sit",
                    "D. run"
                ],
                "answer": "B. stand"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. liedown",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. jumping"
                ],
                "answer": "C. crouch"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sit",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. stand",
                    "D. wave"
                ],
                "answer": "C. stand"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. liedown",
                    "D. pointing"
                ],
                "answer": "C. liedown"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in camo vest relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-right of",
                    "B. To the front-left of",
                    "C. Above",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Below"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the right of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the back-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. In front of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Below and to the front-left of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Above and to the back-right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Above and to the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Slightly below and to the back-left of",
                    "B. Slightly above and to the front-right of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. Slightly below and to the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Above"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the woman in camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the back-right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the back-right of"
            }
        }
    }
}